You have no items in your shopping cart.

  Search

Close

    * back

    * back

    * back

    * back

    * back
    
* Products

Menu

    * back

    * back

    * back

    * back

    * back
    
* Products
    
    * back
        
        * back

Menu

Personal menu

My account

Filters

Search

Privacy policy
==============

### General Statement of Principles 

This Privacy Policy applies to the MicroBarBox websites and its subdomains (“Sites”). MicroBarBox (MicroBarBox,” “we,” or “us”) knows that you care how information about you is used and shared. This Privacy Policy explains what information of yours will be collected by MicroBarBox when you access the Sites and MicroBarBox Service (including through the websites of our partners), how the information will be used, and how you can control the collection, correction and/or deletion of information. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information we collect by other means (including offline) or from other sources. 

MicroBarBox is responsible for all transactions on this website, however we use SagePay to securely handle all transactions (see details below). If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption. Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards. The whole of our website is hosted on a secure server under a SSL certificate.

Our website and in particular how we store and use your data follows the 2018 General Data Protection Regulations.  

As described in detail below, any information we gather on this web site is strictly for our use and is not shared with any other entity, public or private, for any reason. We will not sell or give away any lists or other data that we may retain and we do not purchase such information from other sources.

**Statistical Data** 

Our servers track IP addresses and referring pages to help with site maintenance and improvements. This data is viewed only as anonymous statistics to show the busiest times of the day or week, pages with errors and how effective our advertising has been. This information is not used for any other purpose.

**Personal Information Collected - Order Forms**

With the exception of credit card info, we store the information from your order form to allow us to track consulting issues or refer to a previous order to help provide some customer service. 

**Information Correction or Removal** 

If you wish to correct, update or remove any information about you that may be in our records, please send us e-mail at [\[email protected\]](https://www.microbarbox.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) with the details of your request. If you wish to contact us further, please find complete contact information on our contact page.

### SECTION 1 - WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?

When you purchase something from our store, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address.  
When you browse our store, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system.  
Email marketing (if applicable): With your explicit permission, we may send you emails about our store, new products and other updates.

**1.1 Information We Collect.**

(a) Our Service: We may collect personally identifiable information about you, such as your full name, phone number, email address, or similar, when you register for an account. If you choose to purchase a product from us, we or our third-party payment processors will collect your payment information. 

If you opt in to receive promotional and marketing emails we will occasionally send you these emails, If you no longer wish to receive these emails, you may opt out of them by unsubscribing at any time from within the footer of the email. When you purchase something from us we may send you service related emails related to your account. If you no longer wish to receive these emails, you may opt out of them by canceling your account.

(b) Cookies And Tracking Technologies: Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by MicroBarBox and our partners (such as advertising, marketing and analytics), affiliates or analytics or service providers. These technologies may be used in analyzing trends, administering the Site, tracking users’ movements around the Site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by such companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis. We also use such technologies to deliver advertisements to you. We use cookies to remember users’ settings as well as for authentication and analytics. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. 

If you reject cookies, you may still use our Site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our Site may be limited. 

We also use Google Analytics, Google Tag Manager, Google AdWords (Conversion Tracking), LinkedIn (Conversion Tracking), Facebook (Conversion Tracking). Some or all of these tools may be used to track information about your behavior on our website depending on your region. For more information or to opt-out, please visit the respective website(s) of these vendors or contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.microbarbox.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

**1.2 How We Use Your Information.** 

We use the information that we collect to operate and maintain our Site and the MicroBarBox Service, send you marketing communications, respond to your questions and concerns and to help us improve our online offerings.

**1.3 How We Share Your Information.**  
(a) Personally Identifiable Information: MicroBarBox will not rent or sell your personally identifiable information to others. We may store personal information in locations outside the direct control of MicroBarBox (for instance, on servers or databases co-located with hosting providers). Any personally identifiable information you elect to make publicly available on our Sites or the MicroBarBox Service, such as posting comments on our review page, will be available to others. If you remove information that you have made public on our Sites or the MicroBarBox Service, copies may remain viewable in cached and archived pages of our Sites or the MicroBarBox Service, or if other users have copied or saved that information. 

(b) Non-Personally Identifiable Information: We may share non-personally identifiable information (such as anonymous usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third parties to help them understand the usage patterns for certain MicroBarBox Services and those of our partners. 

(c) Instances Where We Are Required To Share Your Information: MicroBarBox will disclose your information where required to do so by law, if subject to subpoena or other legal proceeding or if we reasonably believe that such action is necessary to (a) comply with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement; (b) to enforce our Terms of Service or to protect the security or integrity of our Service; and/or (c) to exercise or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of MicroBarBox, our users or others.

(d) Behavioral Targeting / Re-Targeting: We partner with third parties to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partners may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this Site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. The only way to completely “opt out” of the collection of any information through cookies or other tracking technology is to actively manage the settings on your browser or mobile device. Please refer to your browser’s or mobile device’s technical information for instructions on how to delete and disable cookies, and other tracking/recording tools (to learn more about cookies, clear gifs/web beacons and related technologies, you may wish to visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org and/or the Network Advertising Initiative’s online resources, at http://www.networkadvertising.org). If you access the MicroBarBox Service or Sites on your mobile device, you may not be able to control tracking technologies through the settings.

(e) Testimonials: We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our Site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent, we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.microbarbox.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

### SECTION 2 - CONSENT

**How do you get my consent?**

When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.  
If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.

**How do I withdraw my consent?**

For existing MicroBarBox customers, you can review, correct, update or delete inaccuracies to the information about you that MicroBarBox keeps on file by logging into your account to update your password and information. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements. 

If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.microbarbox.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) 

### SECTION 3 - DISCLOSURE

We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.

### SECTION 4 - STRIPE

We use Sagepay to handle all credit and debit card payments and it is Stripe that stores your credit card data. It is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted.  
Stripe adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover.  
PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers.

### SECTION 5 - THIRD-PARTY SERVICES

In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.  
Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.

**Links**

When you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.

### SECTION 6 - SECURITY

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.

MicroBarBox is concerned with protecting your privacy and data, when you enter sensitive information (such as log in credentials) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). No method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

If you provide us with your credit card information, the information goes directly to SagePay and again is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption. Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards. 

**Compromise of Personal Information.** 

In the event that personal information is compromised as a breach of security, MicroBarBox will promptly notify our customers in compliance with GDPR law.

### SECTION 7 - COOKIES

Here is a list of cookies that we use. We’ve listed them here so you that you can choose if you want to opt-out of cookies or not.  
\_session\_id, unique token, sessional, Allows us to store information about your session (referrer, landing page, etc).

cart, unique token, persistent for 2 weeks, Stores information about the contents of your cart.  
\_secure\_session\_id, unique token, sessional

We also use Google Analytics, Google Tag Manager, Google AdWords (Conversion Tracking), LinkedIn (Conversion Tracking), Facebook (Conversion Tracking). 

These services all use cookies to help deliver their services.

Some or all of these tools may be used to track information about your behaviour on our website depending on your region. For more information or to opt-out, please visit the respective website(s) of these vendors or contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.microbarbox.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

### SECTION 8 - OVER 18's ONLY

Legally, by British law, you must be at least 18+ years of age to purchase anything from this website.

### Section 9 - STORAGE AND PROCESSING. 

Your information collected through the MicroBarBox Service will be stored and processed in the United Kingdom, please note that we will not transfer information, including personal information, to a country and jurisdiction that does not have the same data protection laws as the UK jurisdiction.

### SECTION 10 - CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.  
If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.

### QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION

If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at [\[email protected\]](https://www.microbarbox.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)   
\----

### DISCOUNTS & OFFERS

Join our email list and we will send you a 10% off discount code straight away, and don't worry, we will never share your data. By entering your details here you agree to our [Privacy Policy](https://www.microbarbox.com/privacy-policy).

Wait...

### Information

### My account

### Contact Info

* Unit 4 Hollybrook Road Industrial Estate, Southampton, SO16 6RB
* [\[email protected\]](https://www.microbarbox.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Copyright © 2024 microbarbox. All rights reserved.

All prices are entered including VAT. Excluding [shipping](https://www.microbarbox.com/delivery-and-returns)  

Cookies help us deliver our services. By using our services, you agree to our use of cookies.

OK [Learn more](https://www.microbarbox.com/privacy-policy)
